[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Asian folklore the rhinoceros would stomp out fires in the jungle.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1979 film won the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 52nd Academy Awards in 1980.", "correct_answer": "Kramer vs. Kramer", "incorrect_answers": ["All That Jazz", "Norma Rae", "Apocalypse Now"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie an English auctioneer unwittingly gets involved with his fiances mob family.", "correct_answer": "Mickey Blue Eyes", "incorrect_answers": ["Eyes Wide Shut", "Notting Hill", "The Talented Mr. Ripley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital city of the Netherlands?", "correct_answer": "Amsterdam", "incorrect_answers": ["Amersfort", "The Hague", "Zwolle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following words originated from what language: canoe, hurricane, and hammock?", "correct_answer": "Taino", "incorrect_answers": ["Tagalog", "Techetulan", "Tanzanian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A tendon is a tough band of fibrous connective tissue that connects a muscle to a bone.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Russian biologist Ilya Mechnikov what explained the longevity of certain Bulgarian peasants?", "correct_answer": "The bacteria in yogurt", "incorrect_answers": ["The concentrated calcium in yogurt", "The vitamins in yogurt", "The cholesterol-lowering properties of yogurt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Amy Fowler Kane, Kanes new wife in the film High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Grace Kelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia Mayo", "Carole Lombard", "Susan Hayward"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of Hawaii, the 50th US state?", "correct_answer": "Honolulu", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Rock", "Dover", "Frankfort"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Playboy Bunny outfit, worn by waitresses at the Playboy Clubs, consisted of bunny ears, a corset, a collar, cuffs and what else?", "correct_answer": "Fluffy tail", "incorrect_answers": ["Chains", "Bandana", "Whiskers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do skunks eat in the wild?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "Meat", "Fruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although minimal, the risk of transmitting this disease through a tattoo needle exists. This disease can also be transmitted through the ink or dirty equipment and environment.", "correct_answer": "Hepatitis B", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Cholera", "Mumps"]}]